<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TRA data="1" mask="1" def="-2"/><JUST loc="center"/><TEXT>ZT43-3 "Fury 3" Zoner Photon Blaster</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><TRA data="0" mask="1" def="-1"/><JUST loc="left"/><TEXT>This is a photon-based weapon which, though providing a high refire rate, requires enormous amounts of energy to deliver a significant damage output. This weapon is most effective against positron shields, and weakest against graviton shields. Zoner weapons have a small range advantage, but at a reduced rate of fire. This is the best Photon Blaster the Zoners have to offer.</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>