<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>We will never allow Republican to land at Yokohama, not after all the financial hardship that the Kusari people had to endure during the 80-Years War. Because large amounts of government money were available for advanced weapons research and development, the war did enable us to increase our shielding and cloaking capabilities.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

