<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Can I buy you a drink? I definitely need one. It was a difficult day. My unit was on a deep reconnaissance patrol in the Shiden Cloud, looking for the GC. We were engaged in battle with the GC for 15 minutes, and then they vanished. Our unit lost Takana-san and Ogawa-san. I was just singing karaoke with them last night, so sad ...</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

