<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>We handle all manner of precious cargo bound for the outer colonies. We ship Luxury Goods to New London, New Tokyo, and New Berlin. It is extremely dangerous between New London and here, especially because of the Lane Hackers. They aren't the dangerous part, it's the Outcasts who they sell the shipping information to that you have to worry about. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

