<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Don't be fooled; just because I work for a bankrupt government, that doesn't mean I don't have credits to spend. Several corporations always pay well for the authorities to turn a blind eye to certain actions. I don't open my mouth when Synth Foods burns down one of the few remaining Rheinland plantation houses, and that's how I make sure I'll retire in style. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

