<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The vile Bounty Hunters are everywhere in this system. They're worse than the LPI because they follow only one rule: Secure proof for every Xeno vaporized. They evidently know about the Jump Holes and always hang out in the no-fire zone around Ames. They often ambush us on supply hauls, so we usually send rookies to limit our losses.</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

