<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Because of the financial troubles Rheinland is in, we haven't been making as much profit at this resort as our others. We may be forced to bring in Liberty vacationers. Not the quality types either -- they can go to Hawaii or Curacao.  We’ve had to bring in the econoclass vacationers to fill the rooms.</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

