<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Lane Hackers make attacks upon our vessels in Galileo. They have a base there in the Komatsu Cloud, though its exact position within the cloud is unknown. They are always able to sniff out the most expensive cargoes to seize. We have taken to escorting the most lucrative shipments; sometimes it is not enough just to run patrols.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

