<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The asteroid fields of Magellan were notorious for their unpredictability. The Bretonian government established this base in 220 and called it the Gough Station. Repair and lifter ships were stationed here to assist disabled ships and to remove errant asteroids as they crossed the cleared trade routes. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

