<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>This sure beats the police. I hadn't been paid in two months. The rest of my post had turned to "Trade Lane tolls" that they forced passing ships to pay. Berlin got wind of it and sent the lot of them to Vierlande to discourage others sharing the same thought. I decided to change professions and try to earn some legitimate money. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

