<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I kind of like the Xenos. Truth is I almost joined up with them on a tour of “the Walls,” but I decided to join up with the Rogues instead. But the Junkers will pay me good money or Cardamine to kill Xenos, so if I see one flying solo, then I’ll kill him. If there’s more than one, I don’t pay them much mind. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

