<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The industrial pollution and horrors that have been blamed on Daumann are completely groundless. The Bundschuh and other political terrorists view us as the villains of Rheinland. We have provided generations of Rheinland workers with secure jobs and decent pay. Yet they always want to work less and make more. We couldn't possibly meet their demands and still be profitable. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

