<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>There's good business for the Guild down in Dresden. Daumann and Kruger are both looking for Bounty Hunters to guard their operations. Kruger is the better one because you can always go Diamond mining when no one is looking. You'll earn your keep, though. Plenty of Hessians to go around in Dresden. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

