<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I just finished a very difficult run from the Ring in New Berlin with a load of Daumann-mined Cobalt and Copper. First we have to deal with the Unioners in New Berlin and Hamburg. Then the Xenos take over in Hudson and Texas. Then they hit us again just down the Lane in the Silverton Field. You'd think they wouldn't care about a bunch of ore, but they just hate us. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

