<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>By the end of "the Eighty," the government was more concerned with putting down the rising rebellion than the GMG and the devastated system of Frankfurt. The empire's coffers were drained. On the edge of insolvency, Rheinland borrowed from Liberty and sold away the last of its ability to stand alone. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

