<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Universal Ship Identification (USI) is a system in which ship cargo manifests are downloaded into databases as ships pass through Jump Gates and Trade Lanes. Somehow the Lane Hackers got their hands on the technology and now know which shipments carry the most valuable Commodities, making it easy for them to target specific transports.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

