<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Hessians don't really attack us, so that is good. We don't have to fear for our physical safety, but Gateway does all the shipping to this base and their convoys often get attacked on the way in. So the pirates do make our lives a bit harder sometimes, but I'm not going to try and explain that to the Hessians who come here. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

