<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Danzig is a long lost Kruger freighter that strayed into the Giftnebel in 450 while returning from the Diamond fields. The cloud’s hostile conditions prevented any thorough search. Pieces of debris have been spotted drifting occasionally within the area, but no one has been able to determine if they are the remains of the Danzig. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

