<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>There are some top Hunters of the Guild out in the Omega Sector. I was talking to one of 'em last week on Freeport 1 -- said he'd made it all the way to Freeport 5 in Omega-41. That's on the edge of nothing, that is. He talked about a neutron star's deadly radiation that'll fry ya in a couple of minutes if you aren't properly protected. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

