<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Almost all Kusari shipping stops in Tokyo. My family is here, but I don't see them often. It is a lonely life, that of a tanshin funin. We just brought a load of Niobium from Tau-29. I'm transferring to an armored transport leaving for Hokkaido on a Side Arms delivery to the </TEXT><TRA data="2" mask="2" def="-3"/><TEXT>Matsumoto</TEXT><TRA data="0" mask="2" def="-1"/><TEXT> within the next hour. Hokkaido is not an easy trip. Maybe I'll have some whiskey before I go.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

