<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Kusari-Rheinland embargo was an incident that reminded Liberty that her forces must remain ever-vigilant. We believed our military might to be unstoppable, but we were wrong. Once the H-Fuel stopped flowing into Liberty we could no longer power our attack crafts and had to acquiesce to the demands of the foreign powers.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

