<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>BMM is paying the bill for us to complete the Trade Lane to their mining area. The operation must be costing them a fortune considering the number of Outcast attacks on our construction sites. I'm glad I don't have to go out there and work on the Rings. I'm a desk jockey -- the guy who makes sure we ship all the right supplies to this base, plus I get danger pay. It's a good job. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

