<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Jesse Casas was truly an original. Captured as a young Corsair on his first mission to the inner house systems, he spent years imprisoned in Vierlande. He eventually renounced his Corsair vows and joined the Bounty Hunters Guild. Flying the Rebel, Casas used his intimate knowledge of the pirate ways to full tactical advantage. He finally met his demise somewhere in the Napo Cloud in 791. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

