<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Down here we run Cardamine and H-Fuel from our base in Hokkaido in exchange for many of our basic supplies. Leiden indirectly supplies the Blood Dragon base in Chugoku via Ainu. That's the real reason we have to make so many runs down to this alien place. They often protect us from hostile attacks, so it's worth it. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

