<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Frankly speaking, I do not understand why we must persecute the Blood Dragons so strongly. They are not indiscriminate pirates like the Outcasts or Corsairs, only attacking Kishiro when they need supplies. Samura and the government have a deep hatred for the Dragons that has not diminished over the centuries. So I must follow orders ...</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

