<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>There was a Unioner attack just last week.  They came out of the Alsterfeld, heading straight for one of the freight trains in the dry docks.   The base turrets laid down very heavy fire, but were not able to destroy all the enemy attack force.   Two got through and released their torpedoes.  The freight train </TEXT><TRA data="2" mask="2" def="-3"/><TEXT>Eifel </TEXT><TRA data="0" mask="2" def="-1"/><TEXT>was heavily damaged.</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

