<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Outcasts have been exposed to Cardamine for centuries. They are the key to understanding how the drug affects human beings. If we could understand that better, we could make a less dangerous Cardamine that wouldn't interfere with worker productivity. We could then legally distribute it to the Sirius population. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

