<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The last thing I want to do when I'm in this system is come up against a Corsair. I always start sweating as I'm approaching the Jump Gate out of here. We got jumped three runs ago. I made it out of the system with one escort, but I was too badly damaged to take the Gold to Liberty. I had to stop in New London for repairs. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

