<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>After the Eighty Years War we lost everything. My family worked for Kruger in those days. When the bottom fell out of the economy we lost our jobs and the bonuses that had been promised us. Worse than that, more than half of my ancestors were killed trying to mine gases in contested space. My brother joined the Hessians, but I am not a violent man, I joined Daumann. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

