<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The vermin who call themselves the GMG dealt the first blow in the conflict that would erupt into the Eighty-Years War. The Kruger survey vessel Helle Wolke went missing. When we sent ships after her, we found the GMG in the vicinity of the wreckage. The GMG could not explain what had happened, but claimed to be investigating themselves. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

