<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I hate them Cambridge folks. They are all stuck up cod livers, with their datapads and degrees and their "Oh, I'm a smart one aren't I?" attitudes. Here in Leeds a datapad is best used for breaking over somebody's head. Well, if you wanna run to Cambridge doing the same thing Bowex does, then I recommend picking up some Optronics here and returning with Food. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

