<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>As the number of captured ships grew, we realized that a shipyard was needed to repair damaged vessels and build ships from stolen components and spare parts. We began to gather modules together and steal the goods necessary for the construction of this shipyard, which you can see is quite operational. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

