<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Outside of colony space you don't have the luxury of Jump Gates. You must use Jump Holes to travel between systems. Omega-41 is a crossroads in this part of space. There are Holes that lead to Omega-11 and Omega-5 on the western side and to Omicron Theta and Omicron Gamma in the eastern half. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

