<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Our ancestors are Kusari fishermen that were forced to leave Honshu in the second century, after the fishing stocks became severely depleted. They entered the Crow Nebula in search of something new to harvest. After 20 years of wandering, they found Hydrogen and Helium isotopes that were far more abundant here than anywhere else in the Sirius sector. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

