<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Mollys are smart about their attacks. They attack in several different parts of the system simultaneously so we have to split our forces. The trouble comes from not knowing which attacks have the greatest number of ships. When they attack they do as much damage as they can, and then they split up and get out, making the chase very difficult. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

