<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Naval Forces is somewhat uncertain of our relationship with Samura. Kishiro has shown us more promising research in 10 years at our new center in Kansai than Samura ever has at Nansei. They recently offered to build our ships at the Yukawa yard in Honshu. Given their more advanced shielding technology, this is an attractive proposition.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

