<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The money given to us by the Bretonian government to terraform Harris has already been used up. We would not have the funds to complete this project if we did not divert capitol from other operations to this one. Luckily, we have been able to sell the government on terraforming more than one planet. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

