<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>We use the Jump Hole to Shikoku, then skirt the west end of the system through the nebula clouds to avoid detection by the Blood Dragons -- our mortal enemies. The police and Bounty Hunters rarely bother us. At the far end of Shikoku is a Jump Hole to Kyushu, followed shortly by a Hole to New Tokyo. Very convenient. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

