<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>My brother works for BMM. There is no way I would ever do that work. BMM will work you to death and then dock your pay for sleeping on the job when you keel over. I've got my pride. I don't need some damn overseer yelling at me about corporate profits and what not. It's just me and the Niobium out here. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

