<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>We supply this operation with Optical Chips from Houston. I guess they use them in their Mining Machinery-manufacturing process for control devices. On the return trip to Liberty, we haul the Mining Machinery needed by the Dallas Debris Field prison crews and the Pittsburgh Boron-extraction operation. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

