<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Got me a Rogue ace the other day by the name of Buford "Tex" Wilson. He'd been shooting up a lot of ships along the Trade Lane to the Galileo Gate during the past few weeks. The LPI cornered him once, but he just shot his way out of it. I was patient, waited in the Alamosa Field near the Galileo Jump Hole. When he came through, blammo! That bounty will set me up for a while. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

