<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Kusari State Police prides itself in being a highly ethical organization. Hogosha often attempt bribes when they are caught, but we will never accept them. The bureaucrats of Tokyo are another matter, however. There are many stories of the criminal bribes and gifts that are accepted by the rulers of our nation. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

