<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Our company is not used to being the third into a system. Usually we claim space first. Not so here, but Kruger is in its death throes and the IMG can easily be removed. Of course, if Kruger does merge with ALG they will have the backing necessary to establish control. That must be considered if we are to attempt a major investment. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

