<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Lane Hackers in Galileo are a bunch of pansy rich boys who can’t do their own dirty work. It’s that kind of attitude that has let foreigners come in and take jobs from the Liberty working man. At least they use Rogues to do their work for them and not Kusari pirates. That still makes the Rogues the pawns of the rich and lazy. Lane Hackers don’t know what real work is, how hard it is for so many of us to survive. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

