<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>There's a couple of Jump Holes in this system -- the one to Cortez in the northern part of the system is easier to find. If you wait patiently enough, you can pop a Rogue or two as they come through; they won't even know what hit them. If you see an Outcast, you better have some support, though. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

