<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Ring is one of Rheinland's most famous landmarks. On a clear day, you can see it planetside on Berlin. It is positioned at the La Grange point between Potsdam and Berlin, where the gravitational attraction of the planet and moon effectively neutralize each other. That enables the Ring to maintain a stable orbit with minimal attitude and speed corrections, which would otherwise exert substantial forces on such a large structure. </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

