<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Tokyo Command says that once the Blood Dragons' fire is extinguished, all of Kusari will again be in peace and prosperity. I doubt this. The government is almost bankrupt. Arming the GMG during the 80-Years War was very costly for Kusari. The ongoing difficulties around the Chugoku Gate Construction site have created a new burden on the already depleted Treasury.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

