<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I like visiting this place. Normally I look out my office window in Leeds and can't see anything green through all of the sulfurous clouds. My company's executive office wants to exploit Gaia much as they did with Leeds, with little or no government foresight. I'm not sure that's such a good idea at this point, given our track record. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

