<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Poor Wang, one of my gunners. I don't think he is going to survive. I barely lived myself, but the Outcasts will chase you as far as they can. Luckily we were able to make it to the Jump Gate. Once we entered the system, Mollys almost finished us off. All three of my escorts were dead, but a Bretonian Navy patrol was coming by at the time of our entry. If they hadn't chased off the Mollys, Wang would be dead for sure. I hope he lives, because he is supposed to marry my sister. If he dies, no one will marry her. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

