<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I haul Luxury Food from Cambridge all the way here. You really have to push it to make it before the Food spoils. We typically pick up a load of Luxury Goods for New London on the return. That's less time-sensitive but more dangerous for the Lane Hackers in Cortez and Magellan. They always seem to know when we're coming. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

