<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The most embarrassing epoch in Bretonian military history was the time right after the Founders Day Revolt. The destroyers made the first mistake by following the Mollys into an asteroid field. Even worse was when the Hood made the same mistake and got too badly crippled to make it back home to New London. It was decommissioned and stripped of all weaponry, engines, supplies, and materials. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

