<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>If it was The Order’s mission to disrupt the conference, they did a good job, even if they missed Mr. Obst. Now he says Kusari is trying to kill him? I hear the assassin they captured died in his cell before he could be questioned -- OD’d on Cardamine, injected a massive dose right into his own heart. Surprised they didn’t catch that when they searched him. Pity. I wanted to hear if Kusari really does have ties to The Order.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

