<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Something serious is going on that has to do with the Freeport 7 investigation. My brother, who’s an officer in the LPI, tells me that the police and the LSF are going through the manifest and are actively looking for anyone who was on that station. He said that several people have been incarcerated and that the methods of interrogation are not, well, standard. That’s all he was willing to tell me. For my own protection, he said.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

