<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I hear that the Chancellor has a group of psi-gifted advisors who are now guarding him against any possible danger. They're constantly scouring the minds of those around him and reporting back! Anyone who is even remotely negative towards him is taken away for "conditioning." They're never quite the same after they return.</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> [kw1]What does this mean?</TEXT><PARA/><TEXT> [/af2]Psi: It's short for psionics.  It's not unlike ESP sensitivity or even telekinetic ability. </TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

