<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>You know, there is a whole group of Kusari people -- merchants, pilots, regular blokes -- stuck in Rheinland and not allowed to return home. I hear the local police are leaning on them pretty heavily. They're being unlawfully detained, questioned, searched, and their property illegally confiscated. I also hear the Chancellor is starting to see conspiracy everywhere now; he’s even looking for spies in his own family -- people he’s known for years.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

