<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The summit meeting is as good as dead. They’ve killed Quigley, man! I hear people think it’s The Order again. And by the way, I don't believe for a second that that Ballenshine bloke went belly-up all by himself either. Somebody helped him along, and they're just trying to cover it up. That's what I think. I mean think about it. First they kill Liberty’s man, and now ours. What better way to sabotage the summit.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

