<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TRA data="1" mask="1" def="-2"/><JUST loc="center"/><TEXT>ESRB Notice: Game Experience May Change During Online Play.</TEXT><PARA/><TRA data="0" mask="1" def="-1"/><TEXT>You acknowledge and agree that Multiplayer Games are not hosted by or under the control of Microsoft. You acknowledge and agree that Microsoft has no control over or responsibility for your experience while in Multiplayer Games, or any content or other information or data you may create, encounter or receive, including chat, while you are playing Multiplayer Games.</TEXT><PARA/><TRA data="1" mask="1" def="-2"/><TEXT>Do you want to continue?</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

