<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I’ve heard that you’re looking for Doctor Ronald Quintaine. I’ve known him for over twenty years. He’s an emeritus Professor of Archeology and Pre-Human Colonization at Cambridge University. His main interest for the last twenty years has been the study of Alien Artifacts. Many people consider him the foremost authority in that field. I haven’t seen him in a few weeks, but I’m sure he’s crawling around some ruins somewhere in the Border Worlds.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

