<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Hovis? Yeah, I know him. He’s undefeated in these races you know. In fact, that’s all he does. He was exiled from Liberty for illegal gambling and for rigging a bomb on the bottom of a ship. The problem was that ship was racing him at the time and was piloted by a major senator’s son. He’s been here ever since. I’d watch my back around him. He’s not exactly right, and as much as he loves to race, he loves winning even more -- if you get my meaning.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

