<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>I remember there was this girl Vanessa -- a gorgeous creature with legs that didn’t stop. Smart, too. She’s a student at Cambridge. She used to go out with this total space case named Trent. I think he broke up with her because of some kind of  “deal of a lifetime.” What an idiot. While money comes and goes, a good woman is impossible to find.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

