<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>What they’re not telling us is that the Rheinlanders aren’t just sending some ships over. They’ve developed a new kind of ship -- one that can cloak. That's what I heard, at least. Got a friend whose brother works for the Signals Corp. He says they’re worried, and with good reason. It’s the perfect recon and first strike weapon. No evidence -- total surprise.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

