<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>A medic friend of mine told me that the LPI took all of the Freeport 7 survivors to LSF headquarters for interrogation. He also told me that he spoke to one of these survivors, a man named Lonnigan, who said that the station was attacked by some strange-looking ships that were unlike anything he'd ever seen before.  Strange huh?  Well, he was also muttering something about the government being "behind it all", whatever that means. That Lonnigan guy was supposedly in pretty bad shape -- but you never know, maybe there’s some truth to what he was saying.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

