<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TRA data="65281" mask="-31" def="30"/><TEXT>&gt;&gt;&gt;CAUTION&lt;&lt;&lt;</TEXT><PARA/><TRA data="96" mask="-31" def="-1"/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT>At the heart of this dense asteroid field lies the LD-14 uranium processing center, responsible for producing the majority of MOX used by Bretonia and Kusari. The asteroid field and its pockets of radiation provide natural protection against attempts to raid the facility, while the automated defense platforms ringing the facility offer further deterrence.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

