<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The Shikoku system was originally a gateway for almost all of the traffic originating from Liberty and the independent worlds. Entry requirements for the New Tokyo system were initially very strict, and as a result, Shikoku became home to a large band of itinerant foreigners. Deshima Station was constructed in 350 AS to house this population, and despite the significant relaxation of New Tokyo system entry requirements, it still serves as a way station. Over the years Deshima has been substantially improved through the addition of a Synth Foods biodome, the construction of additional living space, and a partnership with Kishiro to manufacture Consumer Goods. The Bounty Hunters Guild also recently opened an office here as the large numbers of foreigners in the system includes a significant criminal element.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

