<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Constructed in 603 AS by Kishiro, Nago Station is one of Kishiro’s primary sources for the Hydrocarbons needed to fabricate the Polymers used in Optical Chips. Optical Chip manufacturing is one of Kishiro's major business sectors, and Kishiro depends on a supply of Polymers to manufacture them. The station also houses a standing security force to repulse frequent attacks by pirates and protect its interests from interference by corporate rival Samura.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

