<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Constructed by Samura after the completion of the Jump Gate linking Hokkaido and New Tokyo, Sapporo Station was intended to act as a local base from which Samura could survey the surrounding systems for mineral resources. But with construction proceeding ahead on the Chugoku Gate and the resulting increase in terrorist activity, Samura has been persuaded by the Kusari Shogunate to also house officials from Deep Space Engineering and Universal Shipping while providing support for the Kusari State Police.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

