<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>The spectacular vistas of the Sigma-19 system -- said by many to be among the most beautiful in all of Sirius -- did not go unnoticed by the tourist industry for long, and in 791 AS Orbital Spa and Cruise Lines stationed its state-of-the-art luxury liner Hawaii in the system. An incredibly popular destination, the Hawaii has operated at near capacity almost from the beginning. The location of the ship outside the policed boundaries of the colonies is also rumored to be part of the attraction, and much of the popularity of the Hawaii lies in the implied promise of forbidden fruit available to those who can afford a ticket.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

