<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Freeport 4 was originally a Bretonian station that was abandoned but later reopened by unemployed miners from New London. The miners eventually joined the Independent Mining Guild (IMG) and declared the station a Freeport, open to all. The population largely subsists on whatever income it can manage by selling Water and ice to the IMG, freelancers, or anyone else who has the credits, and by repairing the odd commercial transport damaged by asteroids or pirate raids.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

