<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TRA data="1" mask="1" def="-2"/><JUST loc="center"/><TEXT>HIGH TEMPERATURE ALLOY</TEXT><PARA/><TRA data="0" mask="1" def="-1"/><JUST loc="left"/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT>High temperature alloys are essential to the construction of engine components: only a material with the strength of cobalt and the temperature resistance of niobium could withstand the tremendous amount of heat and pressure that exists within the combustion chamber of a fusion engine. However, the rarity of niobium and the complex fabrication methods employed mean that high temperature alloys are relatively expensive -- but without them, modern space travel would be impossible.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

