<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Canterbury Station houses the headquarters for Planetform, Inc., a pioneer in transforming uninhabitable or marginally habitable planets into terrestrial worlds. With the sparseness of arable planets outside of the core systems claimed by Liberty, Planetform, Inc. has been conducting a considerable amount of business in Bretonia and elsewhere. However, its operations have recently come under attack by Gaian eco-terrorists, and by necessity security guidelines have grown more stringent.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

