<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TRA data="1" mask="1" def="-2"/><JUST loc="center"/><TEXT>LUXURY CONSUMER GOODS</TEXT><PARA/><TRA data="0" mask="1" def="-1"/><JUST loc="left"/><TEXT> </TEXT><PARA/><TEXT>There are always those with money or influence who demand items that will set them apart from -- and above -- those without their resources. For such individuals, Luxury Consumer Goods offer the ultimate status symbol and include big ticket items such as jewelry, designer clothes, and advanced Optronics. All of these items are valuable precisely because they are rare, often fabricated from the most uncommon or difficult-to-obtain resources in the Sirius Sector.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

