<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Settled in 5 AS, New Tokyo is the capitol of the Kusari Empire and, with nearly two hundred million people clinging to its scattered islands, its most populous planet. Despite -- or perhaps because of -- this crowding, New Tokyo is a vibrant world with centuries of history and some of the most advanced technology in the colonies. It is also a culture in transition, as bureaucrats and corporations wrestle with the best ways to manage the rapidly increasing pace of change. To accomplish this difficult task, the Kusari ruling body, the Shogunate, works closely with corporate </TEXT><TRA data="2" mask="2" def="-3"/><TEXT>keiretsu</TEXT><TRA data="0" mask="2" def="-1"/><TEXT> -- such as Samura and Kishiro -- to advance the interests of the Empire while safeguarding the heritage of the Kusari people.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

