<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-16"?><RDL><PUSH/><TEXT>Junyo is almost entirely covered by a deep ocean that remains liquid across the planet's entire surface due to the young, hot Shikoku sun. While initially dismissed as infeasible for further development, the impending collapse of fisheries throughout Kusari in 630 AS motivated the government to begin terraforming the planet using recently discovered Alien Organisms in order to jump-start the nascent ecology. Within 50 years, the planetary environment had been sufficiently altered to begin wide-scale production of Luxury Foods under the administration of Samura, a company that refuses to concede the market to the competing Liberty firm of Synth Foods.</TEXT><PARA/><POP/></RDL>

